Muhammad Rifqi

Indonesia-based with a background in computer science, interested and focused on UI/UX design. Prioritizing user's experience, I'm Designing to solve problems efficiently. Looking ahead to a further future, one small step at a time.

odorifqi@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/odorifqi odorifqi.github.io

Portfolio

BAXY (UI/UX Case Study) Link

BAXY is a workout app where users can do, make, organize and share workout exercise. Experienced user also can contribute more by creating online coaching session

What is gestalt? (Article) Link

Summarizing about my learning result of Gestalt Principle and its implementation in design.

Discoverability and understanding (Article) Link

Sharing about my reading of the topic from the book of Don Norman, "The Design of Everyday Things".

HSB/HSV color system (Article) Link

Explaining hue, saturation, brightness for implementaion in design.

Experience

Dec 2019 - Jan 2020

Web developer (Student Internship)

PT. Pupuk Sriwidjaja

Nov 2017 - Dec 2018

Head of HR (Student Organization)

Student Executive Board of CS Faculty

Mar 2017 - Oct 2017

PIC of Equipment and Security (Event)

Technology Euphoria 2017 of CS Faculty

Feb 2017 - Oct 2017

Staff of HR (Student Organization)

Student Executive Board of CS Faculty

Education

Aug 2016 - Jun 2021

Bachelor of Computer Science

GPA: 3.38

Sriwijaya University

Competency

- > Product Design
- > Prototype Design
- > Interaction Design
- > UI/UX
- > HTML
- > CSS
- > Javascript
- > ReactJs

Tools

- > Figma
- > Visual Studio Code
- > Github

Language Proficiency

- > Bahasa Indonesia (Native)
- > English (Working proficiency)